Hello.
こんにちは
Frilly is super cute.
フリフリはすごい可愛いです
It's cute, isn't it?
可愛いですよね
The frilly frills on the chest are also really cute.
胸元のフリフリもすごい可愛いです
Do you like black?
黒が好きなのですか?
That's right.
そうなんです
The glasses are also black...
メガネも黒で...
That's nice.
いいですね
Do you feel intelligent?
知的な感じがしますか?
yes.
はい
You were a university student.
大学生でしたね
that's right.
そうです
Is the screen difficult?
難しい画面ですか?
No, it's an art school.
いや、美術系ですよ
That's right.
そうなんですね
The picture...
絵が...
Sculpture...
彫刻...
What?
何が?
drawing.
デッサン
Drawing...
描くのが...
amazing...
すごい...
I like it.
好きです
I'm good at it.
上手です
I'm not very artistic.
僕はね、 絵心ないんでね
When I draw people, my hands tend to be long.
人間描いたら手が長かったりするんですけど
What kind of things do you draw?
どんなものを描いたりするんですか?
It's a biological painting.
生物画ですね
people?
人?
動物?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Write something quiet...
静かなものって書いて...
Is that so?
そっちか
That's it.
そっちです
A serious-looking person took a photo of Apheid today.
真面目そうな人が 今日はエイフェイドを 撮影していただいた
But.
んです けど
Are you interested in naughty things?
エッチなことは 興味があるんですか?
yes.
はい
By the way, of course you have experience with men, right?
ちなみに、 男性経験はもちろんありますよね?
There is.
ありますよ
How many people?
何人くらいですか?
2 people.
2人
2 people?
2人?
What was your first experience?
初体験は?
What was it like?
どんな感じでした?
Do you remember?
覚えてます?
Even though I was so nervous at the time, I don't remember anything.
その時緊張しすぎても 何も覚えてないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
yes.
はい
Do you remember if it hurt?
痛かったとかは覚えてます?
I agree.
そうですね
It probably hurt at first.
最初の頃、多分 痛かったかな
Did it feel good from the beginning?
最初から気持ちよかったですか?
Maybe.
もしかして
No, that's right.
いやー、そうです
Did it feel better and better?
どんどん気持ちよかった?
It's like that.
そんな感じです
Usually, I just say something like, ok?
普段は、 じゃあ、 おなりとかってします?
Yes, I will.
はい、します
oh.
お ー
How many times a week?
週何回くらい?
At many times.
多い時で
How many times a day do you do it?
1日何回もするんですか?
At most times, I do it several times a day.
多い時だと、1日何回かしてます
I look forward to it every day.
毎日期待します
The days are so different.
そんな、日はバラバラです
The days are different.
日はバラバラ
However, the days are different and I feel like I make a lot of mistakes in one day.
でも、日はバラバラの時で 1日にする過失が多いって感じです
You're getting married.
結婚するんですね
Do you feel like you just keep begging until you're satisfied?
満足いくまで、 おなりし続けちゃう感じですか?
I agree.
そうですね
Are you trying to imagine something?
なんか、想像して、 見てするんですか?
While watching?
見ながら?
Are you watching naughty videos?
見ながら、 エッチなビデオですか?
yes.
はい
Very naughty videos of young people.
なかなか若者の エッチなビデオ、
There are a lot of barres.
バーレが多いもんなんで
You watch naughty videos and then masturbate.
エッチなビデオを見て、 おなりするんですね
The point where it feels good is that it feels like it's being held down.
気持ちいいポイントは、 押さえてる感じです
By yourself.
自分で
Where is it?
どこですかね?
At the gap.
隙のところ
Oh, are you embarrassed?
あ、恥ずかしいですか?
I'm a little sorry.
ちょっとごめんなさい
I'm too embarrassed to say that I eat food
なかなか、 食いトイスって、 なかなか恥ずかしくて言えない
It's true.
です もんね
Does Yakuri-chan feel good?
やくりちゃんが気持ちいいんですか?
I know you have some experience, but do you have a favorite Thailand?
経験あるってことなんですけど、 好きなタイとかってあります?
I like the back.
バックが好きです
back?
バック?
Is it because the angle is good?
角度がいいからですか?
Does it feel like it goes all the way in?
奥まで入る感じ?
that's right.
そうです
I like the back.
奥が好きなんですね
That's naughty.
エッチですね
Is that so?
そうなんですかね
Have you had sex recently?
最近エッチはしましたか?
Is it recent?
最近ですか?
I don't know these days.
最近は知ってないです
That's right.
そうなんですね
Do you tend to do a lot of cussing?
おなりで、 カスターンすることが多いんですかね?
that's right.
そうです
I can see a glimpse of my panties.
チラチラ、パンツが見えちゃってるんですけど
is that so.
そうですか
Are the pants white?
パンツは白なんですかね?
white.
白
Because I can't see well.
よく見えないので
white.
白
Blue?
ブルーか
I agree.
そうですね
That's cute underwear.
可愛らしい下着ですね
Right away, can I have you put on your underwear?
早速ですが、 下着姿になってもらっていいですか?
got it.
わかりました
It's slow.
ゆっくりですよ
I can't help but want to have sex soon.
早 くエッチがしたくてしょうがないんです
Should I be in a hurry?
焦らなくていいですか?
yes.
はい
sorry.
すみません
It's slender.
細身ですね
Is that so?
そうですかね
Do you have any kind of fetish?
何か、 性癖とかあります?
Sexuality?
性癖?
I get excited when something embarrassing happens to me,
恥ずかしいことをされて、 興奮するとか、
Is there something?
何かあります?
Do you get excited by being hit?
叩かれて興奮する?
there is.
あります
What do you have?
何があります?
When I get spanked.
お尻叩かれると
Wouldn't it be great if you got your ass spanked from behind?
バックでお尻叩かれたら最高ですか?
The waist is nice too.
くびりもいいですね
In a bright place, wearing underwear is
明るいところで、 下着姿になっているのは、
What do you think?
どうですか?
It's something I'm not used to.
何か、 慣れないですね
Does your wrist feel good?
手首は気持ちいいですか?
Are you tightening it?
締めてます?
I'm tightening it.
締めてます
Is it easy to apply?
塗りやすいですか?
yes.
はい
Can I have a look?
見せてもらっていいですか?
It's tight.
ぴちぴちになっています
That's a beautiful waist.
きれいな腰ですね
The waist is also very soft.
腰もすごい柔らかい
I don't really have any experience with this.
こっちは、 さすがに経験ないです
I'm embarrassed to have my waist seen.
腰見られて恥ずかしいです
Yes, it's embarrassing.
はい、恥ずかしいです
Did you bring it for me?
取ってきてくれたんですか?
Can I take it?
取 っていいですか?
There's a lot piling up here.
こっちのうちに、 いっぱい溜まっています
I like it now.
今、好きなんです
What are you doing now?
今、何されていますか?
now?
今?
手紋?
Is it different?
違うんですか?
It's a palm print, but is your finger known as a pussy?
手紋ですけど、 指でおまんこ知られていますか?
You understand quite a bit of technical terminology.
結構、専門用語、 わかるんですね
Is this also a technical term?
これ、専門用語もですか?
yes.
はい
After all, speaking of Nets Navi,
やっぱり、 ネッツナビといえば、
I want to show you a lot.
いっぱい見せたくなります
sorry.
ごめんなさい
A while ago.
もうちょっと前
sorry.
ごめんなさい
What?
なん ですか?
air
気
Is it okay to hold it?
持 ちいいですか?
It feels good.
気持ちいいです
Do you like this kind of thing?
こういうのは、 好きですか?
I've never used it before.
あんま使ったことがないです
I think it's the back system.
バックの体制だと思います
There is a child who is suddenly scared.
いきなり怖い子がいます
It's really bad.
すっごい悪しいです
Did you memorize the video?
ビデオを覚えて、 覚えたんですか?
that's right.
そうです
That's what I thought when I watched the video.
ビデオを観て思いました
How is Chin Chin after a long time?
久々の、 チンチンはどうですか?
It's been a while, how are you doing?
久々の、 どうですか?
Lick it.
舐めて
Are you happy?
嬉しいですか?
Compared to the two people I dated,
付き合った二人のチンチンと比べて、
What do you think?
どう ですか?
Compare?
比べて?
Do you want it in your pussy?
おまんこに入れてほしいですか?
I would like you to include it.
入れてほしいです
Ching Chin, can't wait?
チンチン、待ち遠しいですか?
yes.
はい
Is it usually rubber?
いつもは、 ゴムですか?
Always rubber.
いつもゴム
Today, my normal stomach feels good.
今日は、正常胃も気持ちいいです
A normal stomach also feels good.
正常胃も気持ちいいです
it hurts?
痛い?
It tickled.
くすぐった
sorry.
ごめんなさい
How was it?
どうでしたか?
It felt really good.
すごく気持ちよかったです